YAKIMA TENG

Location: Shanghai

Email: veryplans@gmail.com

Phone: 184-5801-9856

HomePage: http://www.yxeye.com/

PROFILE

Job objective: frontend web development, Shanghai, 18K+, and friendly colleagues ^_^

A man from Zhejiang, born in 1991. Self-motivated. Efficient in work. Enjoy writing (have an 8-year blog), reading (130 books till now) and playing badminton.

SKILL

Works are listed in http://www.yxeye.com/cv/.

Familiar with common JS libraries/frames: VueJS2 ***** > React/React Native *** > AngularJS 1**;

Skilled in hand-writing CSS (responsive design, LESS, flex, animation);

Had experience in developing a simple backend server with NodeJS (express) and MySQL;

Comfortable with ES6, webpack/gulp, eslint, flow, git, jQuery, command line tools.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Web Developer @ 北京无线天利有限公司上海分公司 | Dec 2015 - Present

- Frontend web development especially for SPA (i.e. single page application) in WeChat and Android/iOS APPs, and for traditional admin webpages in PC clients;
- Had independent developing experience in VueJS 1/2 for more than half a year;
- Participated in a long-term project outsourced by China Pacific Insurance using ReactNative+Redux;
- Maintained a Angular1 project.

Regulatory Affairs Person @ Zhejiang Apeloa Kangyu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. | Oct 2013 – Jul 2015

 Participated in audits by FDA and WHO. Provide submission for pharmaceuticals registration to foreign regulatory authorities, e.g. WHO, MOH of Ukraine, Taiwan Food and Drug Administrations.

EDUCATION EXPERIENCE

2009 - 2013: Graduated from Shenyang Pharmaceutical University with a B.S. degree in Pharmacy.

Before 2013: Skipped to junior middle school, recommended for admission to senior high school.